Viewers all over the world,
right now, in His faith, begin to thank Jesus for a glorious answer to your prayer.
While you are waiting to be healed, thank Him for healing you.
While you are waiting to be delivered, thank Him for delivering you in His faith.
In His faith.
Thank You, Lord!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Hallelujah.
This is to show that you are forgiven.
Say, "I am forgiven".
If the Son has forgiven you, you are delivered.
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
From every reproach, from every shame - be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Give thanks to Him.
In every prayer, give thanks to Him.
In His faith, give thanks to Him.
Be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
From every reproach, every shame - be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Wherever you are, whatever you are doing, from every reproach, every shame -
be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
You are delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Agree with me - I can see you being delivered.
Your children have come.
You said, "Come unto Me, all ye that are sick".
They have come.
Release them, in the name of Jesus!
Flush out that poison, disease, fibroid!
Diseases in their kidneys, liver - I command them out!
Out!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Whatever satan might have used to connect you to sickness, infirmity, disease - be disconnected!
Whatever satan might have used to connect you to barrenness, infirmity -
be disconnected, in the name of Jesus!
Be loosed, in the name of Jesus!
I can see you being loosed.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Begin to thank the Lord in His faith.
Thank Him for your freedom.